[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 35,
		"Task": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0210a_Barkeep",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_Obelisk_11",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_quest_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 30,
		"Task": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_1a",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 31,
		"Task": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_2",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 29,
		"Task": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_2",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_02_Belly",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 20,
		"Task": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_3",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_01_Location",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 28,
		"Task": "02A_Side04_01_Location_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_01_Location_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 29,
		"Task": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 30,
		"Task": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_01_Tea",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 32,
		"Task": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_2",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_02_Achene",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_3",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_01_Bears",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_27",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_01_Memories",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 28,
		"Task": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_02_Death",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 29,
		"Task": "02A_Side07_02_Death_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
		"AchievementId": "02_Quest_30",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_02_Death_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 28,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_0249a_02_Aethelwynn",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 29,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2a",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_03_Music",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 30,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_03_Music_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_3",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_03_Music_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 32,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_5",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_06_Heart",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 34,
		"Task": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
		"AchievementId": "02A_SQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_title",
		"Description": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]